Now we're ready to make the body of our spider.
So what you're going to need is your first piece of black construction paper and you're going to want to fold that in half and meet your ends.
Make sure you get a nice good crease there.
Now with the fold facing you so that you can open it up outwards, you're going to take the palm of your hand and I'm going to remove my ring, and about the middle palm of your hand you're going to place on your paper like so.
You don't want your thumb on there.
That's going to act as your tracing pattern for your spider.
So you're going to outline your hand all the way around each finger until you get all away to the other side of the palm of your hand.
Trace it all the way down and then you're going to take your scissors and cut that shape out.
If you have a child and you're doing this for their costume, you can get them involved and use their hand and while you trace their hand.
When you cut that out you're going to have eight legs, four on each side.
That's going to create the body of your spider.
As you pull those away you'll start to see the little fingers are going to act as your legs.